abl.com.pk 2016-09-27

# Privacy Policy – Allied Bank Limited

We encourage visitors/clients to check ABL’s corporate website for any updates to the Bank’s Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy outlines how Allied Bank Limited manages its customer’s personal information received through [www.abl.com](https://www.abl.com/ "Allied Bank Limited"). It also describes the sorts of data held, including how it is gathered, maintained, used, and disclosed.

We encourage visitors/clients to check ABL’s corporate website for any updates to the Bank’s Privacy Policy.

#### Collecting Personal Information

ABL collects only personal information necessary for the Bank to conduct its business operation. The Bank obtains information from the following sources:

  * Information received from [Complaints](https://www.abl.com/contact-us/complaints/), [Enquiries](https://www.abl.com/contact-us/enquiries/), [Requests](https://www.abl.com/contact-us/requests/), [Suggestions](https://www.abl.com/contact-us/suggestions/), and [Write to Us](https://www.abl.com/contact-us/) forms
  * Information received from Job Applications
  * Information authorized by clients to us, to resolve their queries or review their online transactions with us.

#### Using Client’s Information

The Bank may use personally identifiable data collected through www.abl.com to:

  * Contact Users/Clients regarding products and services offered by Allied Bank Limited
  * Enhance Users’ experience, &
  * For research regarding the effectiveness of the website, marketing campaigns, and advertising and sales efforts.

#### Maintaining Client’s Information

ABL recognizes that the proper use and safeguarding of personal information is an important social responsibility. As such, ABL makes every effort to ensure that customers’ personal information is properly used and safeguarded with industry standard security measures.

#### Protecting Client’s Information

The Bank stores and manages client’s personal information, endeavouring to keep it current and accurate, whilst employing appropriate security measures and safeguards to prevent data leakages.

ABL also maintains necessary supervision and oversight of resources deployed on www.abl.com who handle personal information.

#### Disclosure to Third Parties

ABL does NOT disclose personal information to third parties without the customer’s consent, unless compelled by law to do so.

ABL reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy or any part thereof at any time, taking into account new developments in information technology, changes in societal demands, and other relevant factors. Through these efforts, the Bank aims to improve management of its customers’ personal information in a more efficient manner. Please check this policy from time to time for any changes.
